<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kids Stories</string>
    <string name="stor_rabbit_name">The Tale of Peter Rabbit</string>
    <string name="stor_cow_name">The Dog Micho and The Lazy Cow</string>
    <string name="stor_duck_name">The Ugly Duckling</string>
    <string name="stor_bee_name">Lazy Bee and Locust Story</string>
    <string name="stor_monkey_name">The Monkey and The Turtle</string>
    <string name="stor_cat_name">The Hungry Cat</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="large">Large</string>
    <string name="medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="small">Small</string>
    <string name="text_size">Text Size</string>
    <string name="cat_story">It was always in the old days. Too old. There was a small cat and beautiful this cat was very hungry, so she entered a house of houses and started looking for food everywhere, and suddenly the owner of the house appeared and was a violent and cruel-hearted woman who did not know the mercy or pity, she grabbed this cat and locked her in a corner in the house, and left her suffering hunger and thirst days and days and strange that whenever this poor cat tried to escape from this house this fierce woman prevented her from that cat and kept the cat in a corner of the house, and left her suffering from hunger and thirst days and days and strange that whenever this poor cat tried to escape from this house this fierce woman prevented her from that cat and kept this cat in a corner in the house, and left her suffering hunger and thirst days and days and strange that whenever this poor cat tried to escape from this house this fierce woman prevented her from that cat and kept this cat in a corner in the house\n</string>
    <string name="monkey_story">There was a beautiful monkey living in the monkey kingdom and taking over the rule, but a young monkey came and expelled the monkey from the referee and took his place and then expelled him from the house of the monkeys forever, and the old monkey went to live on the bank of a river above a tree, and during his eating figs fell big from his hand, he liked the sound of its impact and fall with water, and took to throw more figs and laugh enjoying the sound in the water, and at that time was a turtle in the water, when it was found The fig sought him and ate him with pleasure and the turtle thought, that the monkey was doing it for her and throwing her figs and she was very happy.\n When the husband and her children decided to return, the husband and his wife complained to one of his friends and said to him ask him to turn a monkey and say that one of her children is sick, the turtle returned home, the husband returned to the house and one of her children is sick, the husband said that one of the children is sick and needs the heart of a monkey to heal, so the treating doctor said that, and here the turtle thought about what he says. Husband.\n</string>
    <string name="bee_story">It was a place in the old days, in that remote forest full of many animals, large high trees, there was living in the bee house a group of bees, living in peace and in front of love working and working in a system and love, all bees work hard and active happily and order, except one bee, that bee was very lazy.\n The lazy bee did not like to work, and one day the lazy bee sat at home, refused to go out to work with the rest of the bees, took the bees workhard and active until the end of the day, they worked with love and cooperation, and the queen came and saw all the bees working hard and active.She was very happy and proud of the bees, one of the bees came and said queen, and why the lazy bee does not work and we work hard and every day, she rests in her house without work and does not share with us every day, she said the queen with wonder, and she did not know, any bee so i said bee lazy bee, my lady, she refuses to work, and she sits at home, the queen asked some bee soldiers to bring the lazy bee to her.\n Lazy bees came to the Queen and asked her why you do not work bee like other bees, and prefer to sit at home, said lazy bee, said lazy bee, I do not like work, My Lady, I love rest at home, the Queen said to her: But here in the kingdom of bees, work is the most important thing in our lives, and in our day if you do not work like the bees must get out of the kingdom immediately.\n And here the bee replied: Yes I will get out of the kingdom, the work does not suit me, I will not work, the lazy bee came out of the kingdom after i refused to work like the rest of the bees .\n She went to a very beautiful garden full of red roses, she started sniffing her nectar to enjoy her beauty and happy hess, and here came a little boy who was playing in the garden with his mother behind the bee with greenery, the boy cried with dismay saying: She is a bee that will give birth to me, Mother.\n She came speeding and hit the bee with the book in her hands, strongly with one of the books that she holds the bee fell on the ground injured, the mother took her son and moved away from the garden, and the bee remained alone and injured on the ground can not move she tried to do but she found difficulty in the movement, she remembered her friends and knew the importance of the community and work in it, she wished to go home but she could not move .\n And there was a very large locust, she was flying in the garden and she told her what happened to you bee, the bee said tiredly: One of the ladies and I was hurt and I am severely injured do you carry me to my house, said locust I will carry you my friend, carried by the locust and flew her to her house and entered the lazy bee kingdom.\n Help her friends to treat her and take her to the queen, and the lazy bee apologized to her, I apologize to you Queen I will never live alone and I will work with you and I hope that you will forgive me and accept me again with you what is the most beautiful living in the group.\n</string>
    <string name="duck_story">The big duck marvelled at the sight of this duck and said: What a uglier shape and color, and then i took all the ducks to their father to see them and recognize them, and when their father saw them appeared on the face of the signs of sadness because of this large gray duck and said: I do not want to have this ugly duck among my family members.\n Everyone laughed from the duck and laughed at its bad shape and ugly gray color, so that her brothers began to click her until they expelled her from the place, the duck came out crying sad from the beautiful farm, walked and walked without purpose, and suddenly she saw from afar a beautiful house living in front of him a cat and a chicken, approached them duck and asked them to allow them to live with them for a period of time, the chicken said to her: Can you put the house, then the cat looked at her and asked her Can you hunt mice? The duck shook her head in exile, but if they refused to stay, she could not do anything and there was no use in her existence.\n</string>
    <string name="cow_story">Sultan\'s uncle asked his wife to till the land for agriculture, and then traveled to the nearby village to buy seeds.\n Sultan\'s cousin went to the cow and asked her to go out with her to plow the ground.\n The cow refused to go with Sultan\'s cousin and told her that she would no longer tire of herself and would not plow the land.\n Marzouk\'s wife is confused about the cow, which refuses to plow the land.\n The dog, Michu, learned that the cow did not want to plow the ground and decided to do a trick that would make the cow accept to plow the ground.\n Michu went to the cow and told her that Sultan\'s uncle would make food for the villagers.\n He may be slaughtering it as food for the villagers because it has become useless and does not do its job.\n Sultan\'s uncle may also buy another cow from the market instead to till the land.\n The cow was so terrified by the words of the dog Micho, she rushed to the ground, plowing it into activity.\n Marzouk\'s uncle returned with seeds and the crop was grown on time.\n The cow learned from the dog Micho a lesson you will never forget: in order to live we must work.</string>
    <string name="rabbit_story">Once upon a time there were four little Rabbits,\n and their names were—\n Flopsy,Mopsy,Cotton-tail,and Peter.\n They lived with their Mother in a sand-bank,\n underneath the root of a very big fr-tree.Now my dears,said old Mrs. Rabbit one\n morning,you may go into the felds or down\n the lane, but don\\\'t go into Mr. McGregor\\\'s\n garden: your Father had an accident there; he\n was put in a pie by Mrs. McGregor.Now run along, and don\'t get into mischief. I am\n going out.\n Then old Mrs. Rabbit took a basket and her\n umbrella, and went through the wood to the\n baker\'s. She bought a loaf of brown bread and\n fve currant buns.\n Flopsy, Mopsy, and Cotton-tail, who were good\n little bunnies, went down the lane to gather\n blackberries.</string>

</resources>